HALIL IBRAHIM OZDEMIR

Computer Engineer | Game Developer

hbrahim.ozdemir@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Github | Portfolio

Ankara, Turkey | +905435782844



Computer Engineer with experience in application management and game development. Interned at ROKETSAN, worked on RedHat Linux, WebLogic, IIS, and server setups. Contributed to the Shahmaran project at AnkA Interactive as a C++ Unreal Engine Game Developer.

Work Experience

Game Developer

AnkA Interactive | Ankara

Aug 2023 - Present

- At AnkA Interactive, I worked as a game programmer on SHAHMARAN, a video game developed using the Unreal Engine Responsible for various phases of game development process, including implementing core
- game
 - mechanics, optimizing performance, and providing a seamless experience for players
- Contributed to supporting elements such as user interface design, system logic, and environmental design
- Conducted thorough debugging and troubleshooting to identify and resolve technical issues, ensuring smooth gameplay
- Contributed to the integration process of the game for mobile platforms, optimizing performance and functionality.

IT Infrastructure and Application Management Intern

Jun 2022 - Jul 2022

Roketsan | Ankara

- Worked at Roketsan Application Management Unit, installed WebLogic on Oracle Linux
- Ran an HTML file on IIS after completing the installation
- Performed a DC installation on Windows Server 2019
- Added several computers to the domain name created during DC installation
- Created users on these computers via Active Directory
- Assigned certain permissions to the created users
- Worked on Exchange Server installation

Projects

Revenge: The Dagger

Oct 2022 - Aug 2023

Developed and programmed Revenge: The Dagger, a side-scrolling puzzle game for a university thesis. Led the game's programming efforts, including mechanics, UI, and overall gameplay design, demonstrating strong problem-solving and coding skills.

- Unreal Engine C++ and Blueprint Game Development
- Game Mechanics Programming
- Gameplay Desing
- Level Design

Core Skills

C, C++, C#, Python, Unreal Engine, Unity, Linux, Active Directory, Weblogic, Windows Server, Exchange Server

Education

Alanya Alaaddin Keykubat University

Aug 2020 - Feb 2024

Bachelor of Computer Engineering Computer Engineering

GPA 2.81

Girne American University
Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Oct 2018 - Aug 2020

Languages

Turkish (Native), English (B2), Spanish (A2), Russian(A2), German (A1)

Computer Engineering

Interests

Adventure and Strategy Video Game Genres, Swimming, Comic Books, Movies

REFERENCES

Caner Kurt AnkA Interactive / CEO

Email: trooper@ankainteractive.com

Phone: +90 538 932 57 85

Necdet Aral Roketsan / Head of Application Management Unit

Email: necdetaral@gmail.com

Phone: +90 505 247 80 08

Akın Ozturkcan Roketsan / Lead Engineer

Email: mr.ozturkcan@gmail.com
Phone: +90 507 257 06 33

Ozge Oztimur Karadag Academician at Alanya Alaaddin Keykubat University

Email: ozge.karadag@alanya.edu.tr